[Melody of Golden Age]
[Episode 19]
Jing Lin!
Hasn't the doctor arrived yet?
Jing Lin went to get a doctor.
It's raining too heavily.
It must have delayed them.
No.
If this continues,
he'll lose too much blood.
Butler,
prepare hot water and gauze!
Yes.
♫I hope you also look up and see the radiant stars and moon♫
♫No matter how vast the world is, I'll wait for your appearance♫
♫A quick glance at each other♫
♫Has warmed the winter in memories♫
♫Don't mind the destined solitude, and shine brightly♫
These tools
are what I use
when dealing with the dead.
But desperate times call for desperate measures.
Please don't mind.
♫I'll wait until the years blossom like flowers♫
♫The ice and snow slowly melted♫
♫I heard those tender words♫
♫He told her, "I love you"♫
♫What I saw in my dreams♫
♫Is not a flashy illusion♫
♫I don't fear the challenges ahead, riding a white horse to chase after time♫
♫Let's go together♫
Why is he so feverish?
Butler,
go check
where Jing Lin is.
Let me know when he arrives.
Yes.
♫What I saw in my dreams♫
♫Is not a flashy illusion♫
♫I don't fear the challenges ahead, riding a white horse to chase after time♫
♫Let's go together♫
♫Love is pure and flawless, indifferent to the changes of the world♫
You saved me again.
♫Let's experience it together♫
[Lai Luofu]
Crying is not helpful at all.
It's not helpful at all.
Huo'e can't die in vain.
Shen Du
will get what he deserves.
And Huo'e
will eventually be resurrected.
[Cangming Hall]
Your
Majesties,
overnight, Xiang'an City has been abuzz.
They say
Grand Commander Shen
was publicly assassinated by Chen Huo'e
yesterday
and was fatally wounded.
Back then, Lord Lai
said with certainty
that Chen Huo'e had been executed.
Yet now, a high-ranking official
was severely wounded in front of the people
by someone supposed to be dead.
This isn't just a failure
in the investigation and trial.
It's a slap
in the face of Cang State!
Princess Ying,
everyone knows that Lord Lai
is loyal to Cang State.
And the Imperial Investigation Department has always been strict and efficient.
All this time,
it's been the pillar
of Cang State's authority.
Lord Lai is
the Black Rakshasa that everyone fears.
As for the Imperial Investigation Department, once someone is taken there,
no one has ever dared to disobey.
But Chen Huo'e
has escaped from the Imperial Investigation Department multiple times.
I can't help but suspect
whether Lord Lai
is incompetent
or complicit in it.
Your Majesty, please be clear.
Chen Huo'e indeed died under torture and interrogation
in the Imperial Investigation Department.
The case file
and Chen Huo'e's confession and belongings
have all been submitted by me.
But I heard
although Chen Huo'e was beheaded,
she still had the ability to resurrect.
The people have spread rumors
that one day, Chen Huo'e
will return.
Nonsense.
Madam Xu,
take it out.
Shen Du, the Imperial Security Bureau's grand commander, humbly reports:
I have discovered that Chen Huo'e
is a rare mirror-image person.
She was captured and beheaded on the spot.
There will be no more Chen Huo'e in this world.
A mirror-image person?
Is this
the secret behind
Chen Huo'e's repeated escapes in the past?
Lord Lai, you interrogated her personally,
but you didn't notice the anomaly
of Chen Huo'e being a mirror-image person?
It was my dereliction of duty.
Was it dereliction of duty
or did you think
it was unnecessary to report to me?
I dare not.
I would never
dare hide anything
from you, Your Majesty!
It seems
the pillar of Cang State's authority
should be changed.
Lord Lai, you let a tiger return to the mountain.
Although it was unintentional,
you committed the crime of negligence.
You are fined one year's salary.
And disband
your ostentatious
entourage.
Thank you for your mercy, Your Majesty.
Madam Xu,
send the best imperial doctors
and use the best medicine.
Make sure Mr. Shen recovers as soon as possible.
Yes.
He made such a big mistake,
but he was only fined a year's salary.
Mother is truly lenient
towards Lord Lai.
Your Highness, since you have objection,
why didn't you
raise it in the court earlier?
What do you mean, Minister Zhang?
Minister Zhang.
Sister.
Chen Huo'e committed heinous crimes.
Mother has her own judgment.
It's best not to
discuss it rashly here.
What Prince Xian said is right.
I was too careless.
You always try to be the good guy.
You've lost so much blood.
And you had a high fever last night.
Please, you must wake up.
I haven't cleared
the Shen family's name yet.
♫My heart burned, leaving me cold and forlorn♫
♫And a lifetime of loneliness♫
♫My love blazed. Where did it scatter♫
♫And where did it leave its marks?♫
♫Drifting through the mist♫
♫Amidst the vast, endless waves, I searched in the darkness♫
Why are you here again?
If you're caught, you'll die.
I promised to bring you
♫You passed by, igniting fireworks♫
the cuju balls from the West Market.
When I came in,
they got a bit squashed,
♫For the sake of an end, I embraced silence and became a Shura♫
but they should taste good.
Try them.
♫Love is elusive, piercing you and burning me♫
♫Along the way, flowers bloom and fall, rain pours heavily♫
♫Lights will cross♫
♫You are my destination♫
♫Who will save me from my loneliness and confusion?♫
♫Understanding my fragility, no words are needed♫
I don't have any money on me.
♫Who will save me from my panic and obsession?♫
I'll give you this instead.
I don't want your money.
♫Sheltering my solitude, never letting me fall♫
Do you take me as an errand girl delivering dishes?
♫The chains of fate between us cannot be broken♫
No, I...
This whistle was given to me by my father.
♫Holding the warmth you once gave♫
Look.
There's a Shen character on it.
♫Guiding me to see myself, the person I truly am♫
[Shen]
♫Who will save me from right and wrong?♫
I should leave.
♫Tossed in the sea of people, just hold me tight♫
Otherwise, they'll come to catch me again.
♫Who will save me from grudges and karma?♫
♫Healing my sorrow, never letting me escape♫
Will you come again?
♫The past fades, how many times have we met?♫
Of course.
One day,
I will clear the Shen family's name
♫Who can break free from destiny?♫
and get you out of here aboveboard.
♫I'll cross rivers and leap into fire for you♫
You survived
the hardest days
in the Prisoner's Center.
This time,
you can surely
survive too.
So it really was you.
You can do it.
Grand Commander Shen,
even though you're sick,
you should stay spirited
and wear cool clothes.
Maybe
you can recover faster.
Thank goodness it was you.
I've stitched up the wounds.
Lying here,
he's no different
from any other corpse.
I've dissected so many male bodies.
Why would I feel embarrassed to change his clothes?
[How magnanimous and gentle is he! There he is in his chariot with its two high sides. Skillful is he at quips and jokes, but how does he keep from rudeness in them!]
[Look at those recesses in the banks of the Qi. With their green bamboos, so dense together. There is our elegant and accomplished prince, pure as gold or as tin, soft and rich as a scepter of jade.]
Every night, he placed this rattan-woven pig
under his pillow.
[How magnanimous and gentle is he! There he is in his chariot with its two high sides. Skillful is he at quips and jokes, but how does he keep from rudeness in them!]
[Look at those recesses in the banks of the Qi. With their green bamboos, so dense together. There is our elegant and accomplished prince, pure as gold or as tin, soft and rich as a scepter of jade.]
The handwriting on the letter is delicate.
It must
be from
the woman he can't forget.
Don't worry.
I won't pester you.
You saved me,
and I've been taking care of you.
We're even.
When the three-month period ends,
I'll divorce you as agreed.
Three months?
Divorce as agreed?
What did I just hear?
Chuichui?
Xing.
Why are you here?
With such a big incident,
how could I not come?
Since this morning's court session,
the six ministries have been abuzz.
They say the White Ghost
was fatally injured by Chen Huo'e.
Is he about to die?
He is severely injured,
but...
But what?
I'm so anxious!
Xing,
what exactly happened between you and the White Ghost?
Nothing.
At a time like this,
you still want to hide it from me?
You two... are a fake couple?
Chuichui, you must keep this a secret for me.
I had no choice.
Did Shen Du threaten you?
He must have.
Three months?
Then you can escape
from the White Ghost's lair, right?
That's a good thing too.
But...
given his current condition,
what if he can't
wake up in three months?
Impossible.
He will wake up.
But what if he
can't wake up?
Will you just keep watching over him forever?
He ended up like this
-in order to save me.
-Yes, I know.
But you should also
think for yourself.
What if...
he...
well...
will you live as his widow?
Stop!
What nonsense are you talking about?
-knock on wood.
Since you two are a fake couple,
no matter what happens to him,
you should think about your own future.
Think about it.
When you return to Yan's Mansion in the future,
if you're a divorced woman,
would First Madam
and your siblings
still treat you well?
You and Ms. Jin
would face endless
judgment and exclusion.
I think you'd better
find a good man to remarry.
Well, Chuichui,
what are you talking about?
The Ministry of Justice.
But I don't think in the Ministry of Justice,
there is any good man left to marry.
Jiang Langxing.
Why don't you consider Jiang Langxing?
Jiang Langxing
always
pulls a long face
and is rigid,
but he is indeed a good person.
He is quite adorable sometimes.
He's not bad.
You want me to develop a relationship with Jiang Langxing?
Isn't he good?
Fine.
Let me think harder.
I've thought of someone
more suitable.
Constable Marshal.
Commander Xu
has a humble background,
but he's tall and strong.
And he is generous.
Even if you can't
be the first madam of the Shen family,
being Constable Marshal's wife
would still be impressive.
Xu is a good man,
but he and I
don't have any romantic relationship.
Chuichui, please stop
playing the role of a matchmaker.
A romantic relationship can be cultivated.
Commander Xu
looks like the type
who'd dote on his wife.
That would be great.
Isn't it better than
being with the White Ghost
who always angers you?
I'm just injured,
not dead.
Shen Du,
-you're awake!
-You're awake!
Be careful.
Lu Chuichui,
who are you to talk nonsense
in my mansion?
Get out!
Xing.
-I'll wait for you outside.
-You…
Be careful.
When...
did you wake up?
Just now.
Just now?
Just now, you...
suddenly...
Just now, I
suddenly woke up.
-Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been killed
by Chen Huo'e.
And you got so badly injured because of me.
Chen Huo'e was the one to blame,
not you.
You're the one
who treated my wounds, right?
Where is Chen Huo'e's body?
You were injured at that time.
Jing Lin and I were in a hurry to bring you back.
Chen Huo'e's body
was secretly taken away.
Jing Lin started investigating it immediately.
He thinks it was someone from the Imperial Investigation Department
who took her body away.
Lai Luozhi.
I'm thinking about this.
Chen Huo'e went missing before.
It was Lai Luozhi's dereliction of duty.
Now someone from the Imperial Investigation Department
has stolen
Chen Huo'e's body.
They must be up to something.
We might as well wait for now,
stay still to counter their moves,
and see what they'll do.
Get some rest.
Butler,
Grand Commander has woken up.
Go invite the doctor to come and check on him again.
Master is awake?
Thank God!
God bless him!
Hurry! Go invite the doctor here!
Xing.
Chuichui.
You finally came out.
Go discipline
the servants in Shen's Mansion.
Their madam's good friend is here,
but they haven't even offered a meal.
Lady Lu,
are you short of money?
You have no idea
how good the new play
at Furong Garden is.
The performers were impressive,
so I...
tipped them with my pocket money.
And my father has stopped
giving me pocket money.
And I haven't received this month's salary.
So...
We're good friends.
Just tell me if you're going to treat me to a meal or not.
I can't believe you.
Butler Shen.
Coming.
Madam, what can I do for you?
Please prepare a meal
for Chuichui
and Miss Yun Que.
Also, prepare a meal box.
I'll take it to the main chamber.
Okay.
Yan Xing.
We rarely get to eat together.
Aren't you going to eat with me?
Shen Du is injured and bedridden.
He just woke up and needs someone to take care of him.
There are so many people in Shen's Mansion.
Surely they can manage without you.
Yun Que,
didn't you say
you want to marry the White...
Shen... Shen Du?
Shen Du is seriously injured.
Why haven't you gone to show your care?
Instead, you're here doing nothing.
I've seen through him.
Seen through him?
The White Ghost is not a good person?
He's not a good husband?
But during this time,
I've realized one thing.
Yan Xing,
since you don't want to be Mrs. Shen,
why do you have to waste your life in Shen's Mansion?
Well said!
You two are still
in Shen's Mansion.
Keep your voices down.
Madam,
the food you asked for is ready.
Anyone here?
Yes.
Pass my order.
Since they've all entered the game,
let's give them...
something extra.
Right?
Listen,
he really is very handsome.
You're absolutely right.
You two just had a meal together.
And now you
have become so close?
Yun Que and I hit it off immediately.
It's like we've known each other forever.
We're as close as sisters.
Chuichui and I both believe
only women truly understand women.
Our fate
shouldn't be decided by others.
Exactly.
We should
find our own path forward.
So,
we've decided
to invite you
to go to Mingsheng Temple
to pray for a good marriage in three days.
Go to Mingsheng Temple
to pray for a good marriage?
You don't really want to
be Mrs. Shen for the rest of your life, do you?
Although I'm no longer
interested in Shen Du,
are you and Shen Du
really such a perfect couple?
Is the three-month agreement no longer valid?
Of course it is.
Then why are you being so coy?
Don't tell me...
you've fallen in love with the White Ghost.
When the agreed time comes,
I will naturally leave him.
I'm just focused on my career,
and I haven't thought about remarrying, that's all.
Marriage and career aren't mutually exclusive.
That's right.
In three days,
we'll go to Mingsheng Temple to pray
for a good marriage first, then we'll see.
It's settled.
Oh, right.
In my room,
there are some newly pickled fruits.
I haven't been able to eat much lately.
Would you like to try some?
I'd love to.
-Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Don't miss me too much.
You take it so seriously.
Do you want me to help you choose?
What?
Indeed.
You're seriously injured.
It's indeed inappropriate for me to leave you here and go out.
Later, I'll
deliver those dresses
to Chuichui
and let her choose herself.
I won't go with them in three days.
You're choosing a dress for Lu Chuichui?
Yes.
She's temporarily staying in Shen's Mansion these days.
It's just that
the colors of my dresses
aren't bright enough.
I'm afraid she won't like them.
Since it's an outing among sisters,
you don't need to worry about me.
Shen's Mansion isn't short of manpower.
In three days,
I should be able to get out of bed.
By that time, I'll join you...
No need for that.
You're seriously injured.
You should spend more time recovering.
Get some rest.
I just
watched a couple more plays.
How did I fall asleep?
It must be because
the play was so good
that
I...
It's fine.
It's okay.
Today is truly
a bright
and sunny day.
Oh no!
Are you a human or a ghost?
A ghost.
What's so scary about ghosts?
They were humans when alive.
You may not be afraid of them, but I am.
I'm terrified if you're a ghost.
Every grievance has its source, and every debt has its debtor.
Go find whoever owes you.
Please go away.
Please go away!
Back in the graveyard,
how come I didn't notice
you're so timid?
It's you.
Ghost Face,
this is so strange.
I was so scared just a moment ago,
but when you sat down next to me,
it seems this place
suddenly became less scary.
Maybe because
the ghosts here are afraid of me.
Why are you belittling yourself?
It's the fact.
In this world,
even ghosts, demons,
and monsters are afraid to
cross paths with me, let alone humans.
That's nonsense.
Why are you making it sound so scary?
You're actually very nice.
Look,
it's like
in this void,
even the invisible Little Fairy
wants to be friends with you.
If you don't believe me, watch this.
Pay attention.
Little Fairy, Little Fairy,
do you want to be friends
with Ghost Face?
If you do,
jump from this bowl
to this bowl.
Okay?
You want Ghost Face
to personally invite you?
Ghost Face,
please invite
our Little Fairy.
Please join us, Little Fairy.
Look,
Little Fairy has agreed.
Even Little Fairy is willing
to be friends with you
and play games with you.
You're the most likable.
Everyone will like you.
Alright,
stop crying.
[Bi Luo]
You're the most likable.
Everyone will like you.
And they have to like you.
Yes.
Little Fairy,
since you're also
Lu Chuichui's friend,
can you do me a favor?
Little Fairy has agreed.
What?
Are you scared?
You're
so strange.
You were not scared in the graveyard at midnight,
yet you can be so easily frightened.
I'd say you're timid and afraid of ghosts,
but you're not afraid of my ghost face.
Why should I be scared in the graveyard?
The one lying in that grave is my dearest,
most longed-for mother.
As for you, Ghost Face,
you're unwilling to remove your mask
just because of the birthmark on your face.
That's nothing to be afraid of either.
Oh, right.
I also heard
the method of using a gold ring
to remove a birthmark
doesn't seem to be very effective.
Maybe you shouldn't do that.
If it scratches your face,
it wouldn't be good.
What?
You want to take the gold ring back?
You keep it.
If I can't remove the birthmark,
I'll never dare to show
my true face in front of you.
How could that be?
Having a birthmark isn't your fault.
And one's appearance
shouldn't affect
the beauty of one's inner self.
I think
a person's appearance
is like
the makeup
of a traditional opera role.
It's just a part of the role.
So, what do you think of my appearance?
Is it good
or evil?
Loyal or treacherous?
When you're ready
to take off your mask,
I'll tell you.
If...
If I take off my mask,
but you don't want to look at me,
what then?
Don't worry.
Indeed, I gave you that gold ring
because I hoped you could remove your birthmark.
But whether you can remove it or not
doesn't matter anymore.
Because I've already
considered you a friend.
I certainly won't judge you by your appearance.
You can take it off then.
I'm going to take it off then.
Lai Luozhi.
Lu Chuichui.
Today,
I have shown you my true face.
Whether you are frightened or not,
please keep this a secret for me.
Do not tell
anyone else about this.
Remember what you promised me.
Don't break your promise.
I trust you.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Well...
Xing, look.
[Mingsheng Temple]
So many beautiful ladies
and talented scholars
have come here to pray for a good marriage.
They're here.
What a coincidence!
You've come to pray for a good marriage too?
What?
Only you female officials
from the Ministry of Justice can come here,
but we,
constables, can't come?
Of course not.
I'm just marveling at
how wonderfully
the coincidence has worked out.
Right, Xing?
Stop talking.
Let's go.
Where to?
Didn't you say you're here to pray for a good marriage?
To...
I can't believe it, Nerd Jiang.
You came for that too?
Impressive, Nerd Jiang.
Alright.
You're not young anymore.
It's normal that you want
a beautiful wife in real life.
I, Lu Chuichui, will accompany you.
I'll go with you.
Xing,
have a good chat with Commander Xu.
I'll be right back.
Let's go.
Xing, you rarely come
to Mingsheng Temple for sightseeing, right?
How about taking a walk around together?
You guys go ahead.
Don't worry about me.
[Mingsheng Temple]
Shen Du,
you must drink this bowl of medicine.
Praying for a good marriage at Mingsheng Temple.
Jing Lin.
Grand Commander.
[Mingsheng Temple]
Xu.
Do you have something to tell me?
Xing,
that day, I overheard
Lu Chuichui talking about your marriage.
Is this a joke?
How can a woman propose a divorce?
Why can't they?
Don't forget this.
According to the law of Cang State,
if a husband and wife
are not harmonious and decide to divorce,
it's not a crime.
Besides,
they haven't...
haven't consummated their marriage.
They've already agreed to divorce.
Anyway,
I told her long ago
to find another good man.
It's just that
among you constables
and those from the Ministry of Justice,
no one is suitable,
except for Commander Xu.
One day, I'll tear
Lu Chuichui's mouth.